[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 10, "question": "Who are the bad guys?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "are", "the", "bad", "guys", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 11, "answer": "You can blame Greenspan.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "blame", "Greenspan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Goldman"]}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 16, "question": "What really goes on behind closed doors on Wall Street?", "question_tokens": ["What", "really", "goes", "on", "behind", "closed", "doors", "on", "Wall", "Street", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 17, "answer": "We stand strong, and on the other side we'll eat Goldman's lunch.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "stand", "strong", ",", "and", "on", "the", "other", "side", "we", "'ll", "eat", "Goldman", "'s", "lunch", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "Could it happen again?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "it", "happen", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "I don't think anybody realized that we were within a day away from a major international catastrophic economic meltdown.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "anybody", "realized", "that", "we", "were", "within", "a", "day", "away", "from", "a", "major", "international", "catastrophic", "economic", "meltdown", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "What's the significance of that if anything?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "significance", "of", "that", "if", "anything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "What jumps out at me are the conditions on this bail, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "jumps", "out", "at", "me", "are", "the", "conditions", "on", "this", "bail", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "Given the charges that he's facing, if he is convicted on all seven of these, what kind of sentence are we looking at?", "question_tokens": ["Given", "the", "charges", "that", "he", "'s", "facing", ",", "if", "he", "is", "convicted", "on", "all", "seven", "of", "these", ",", "what", "kind", "of", "sentence", "are", "we", "looking", "at", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "He could be looking at 25 years behind bars.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "could", "be", "looking", "at", "25", "years", "behind", "bars", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "PRP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "What do you make of it, Sue?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "it", ",", "Sue", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "To me the most interesting part of this case is what the state court judge is going to allow in.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "me", "the", "most", "interesting", "part", "of", "this", "case", "is", "what", "the", "state", "court", "judge", "is", "going", "to", "allow", "in", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "Doesn't make it right, though, right?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "n't", "make", "it", "right", ",", "though", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "And we have -- well, we have the First Amendment here, and I will defend the First Amendment.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "we", "have", "--", "well", ",", "we", "have", "the", "First", "Amendment", "here", ",", "and", "I", "will", "defend", "the", "First", "Amendment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "You know, have you heard this rumor?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "have", "you", "heard", "this", "rumor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "Does it seem a potentially credible one to you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "seem", "a", "potentially", "credible", "one", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "I mean how is that a defense?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "how", "is", "that", "a", "defense", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "And that's a very dangerous defense because if you have physical evidence that there was some type of a struggle and evidence that she was in the bathroom with him, and she escaped and she was almost at freedom, but was dragged back, you're putting all your eggs in a basket that may be destroyed by the physical evidence of a fight, of blood in the room, and other types of abrasions on this maid.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "that", "'s", "a", "very", "dangerous", "defense", "because", "if", "you", "have", "physical", "evidence", "that", "there", "was", "some", "type", "of", "a", "struggle", "and", "evidence", "that", "she", "was", "in", "the", "bathroom", "with", "him", ",", "and", "she", "escaped", "and", "she", "was", "almost", "at", "freedom", ",", "but", "was", "dragged", "back", ",", "you", "'re", "putting", "all", "your", "eggs", "in", "a", "basket", "that", "may", "be", "destroyed", "by", "the", "physical", "evidence", "of", "a", "fight", ",", "of", "blood", "in", "the", "room", ",", "and", "other", "types", "of", "abrasions", "on", "this", "maid", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", ":", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "And won't she be wearing a uniform?", "question_tokens": ["And", "wo", "n't", "she", "be", "wearing", "a", "uniform", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Yes, I mean the whole thing -- at the moment there are too many unanswered questions as -- from where we sit.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "mean", "the", "whole", "thing", "--", "at", "the", "moment", "there", "are", "too", "many", "unanswered", "questions", "as", "--", "from", "where", "we", "sit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "Were any of that come when it comes to a divorce settlement now?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "any", "of", "that", "come", "when", "it", "comes", "to", "a", "divorce", "settlement", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Not really.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "So does a lot depend on how she reacts now?", "question_tokens": ["So", "does", "a", "lot", "depend", "on", "how", "she", "reacts", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["California"]}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "What percentage-wise could he expect to lose if Maria goes for the jugular here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "percentage-wise", "could", "he", "expect", "to", "lose", "if", "Maria", "goes", "for", "the", "jugular", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "-NONE-", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "California is a 50-50 state, but if there's no prenuptial agreement and he was spending money, shuffling money to this lady, that gets figured back in the pot.", "answer_tokens": ["California", "is", "a", "50-50", "state", ",", "but", "if", "there", "'s", "no", "prenuptial", "agreement", "and", "he", "was", "spending", "money", ",", "shuffling", "money", "to", "this", "lady", ",", "that", "gets", "figured", "back", "in", "the", "pot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Maria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "This is the L.A. Dodgers owner and his wife, right?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "the", "L.A.", "Dodgers", "owner", "and", "his", "wife", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["L.A. Dodgers"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "And what would you advise him?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "would", "you", "advise", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "I wouldn't give the story legs.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "give", "the", "story", "legs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", ":", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PDT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", "CD", "NNS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "Shock?", "question_tokens": ["Shock", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "I think it's -- really it is so appalling, and I have to say among women -- not that I speak for all women, but the idea that this woman may have had relations with him in their marital bed, that she lived there, that they may have had babies five days apart, I mean, the shocking aspects just keep on coming.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "--", "really", "it", "is", "so", "appalling", ",", "and", "I", "have", "to", "say", "among", "women", "--", "not", "that", "I", "speak", "for", "all", "women", ",", "but", "the", "idea", "that", "this", "woman", "may", "have", "had", "relations", "with", "him", "in", "their", "marital", "bed", ",", "that", "she", "lived", "there", ",", "that", "they", "may", "have", "had", "babies", "five", "days", "apart", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "the", "shocking", "aspects", "just", "keep", "on", "coming", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "This is the woman that for 10 years Maria has been going up to and saying, do I look good in these jeans?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "the", "woman", "that", "for", "10", "years", "Maria", "has", "been", "going", "up", "to", "and", "saying", ",", "do", "I", "look", "good", "in", "these", "jeans", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "CC", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Maria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "I mean wouldn't it have been better for him initially when the baby is born to own up to what happened and to be the father to this boy?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "would", "n't", "it", "have", "been", "better", "for", "him", "initially", "when", "the", "baby", "is", "born", "to", "own", "up", "to", "what", "happened", "and", "to", "be", "the", "father", "to", "this", "boy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RBR", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "TO", "WP", "VBN", "CC", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Because it kind of perfectly encapsulates the mindset of all these guys, doesn't it, on Wall Street?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "it", "kind", "of", "perfectly", "encapsulates", "the", "mindset", "of", "all", "these", "guys", ",", "does", "n't", "it", ",", "on", "Wall", "Street", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "ORKIN: Right.", "answer_tokens": ["ORKIN", ":", "Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "Were they woefully villainous?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "they", "woefully", "villainous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "It's a great question.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "great", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Not very intelligent, or he's willfully now pretending he was those things?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "very", "intelligent", ",", "or", "he", "'s", "willfully", "now", "pretending", "he", "was", "those", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "I think what you realized about Wall Street is these people are professional traders.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "what", "you", "realized", "about", "Wall", "Street", "is", "these", "people", "are", "professional", "traders", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Did you see what happened coming in any way?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "see", "what", "happened", "coming", "in", "any", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "Honest answer, I didn't.", "answer_tokens": ["Honest", "answer", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Did I think that we were going to see a bank like Lehman Brothers go under, that AIG was going to almost falter?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "I", "think", "that", "we", "were", "going", "to", "see", "a", "bank", "like", "Lehman", "Brothers", "go", "under", ",", "that", "AIG", "was", "going", "to", "almost", "falter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", "VBP", "IN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Lehman Brothers", "AIG"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "Do you think professionally speaking now that was a smart move or not?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "professionally", "speaking", "now", "that", "was", "a", "smart", "move", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "It's a personal view.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "personal", "view", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "Wasn't there?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "n't", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "Didn't they?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Well, it was the riding elephant head in the room.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "the", "riding", "elephant", "head", "in", "the", "room", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "Well, I think the hardest part is that this entire financial crisis is a crime unto itself.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "hardest", "part", "is", "that", "this", "entire", "financial", "crisis", "is", "a", "crime", "unto", "itself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Right?", "question_tokens": ["Right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "Needed to add some strings.", "answer_tokens": ["Needed", "to", "add", "some", "strings", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "OK?", "question_tokens": ["OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "The lawyers just want to rack up money.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "lawyers", "just", "want", "to", "rack", "up", "money", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush"]}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "Or is it President Obama who went -- he sorted the mess, didn't put the regulation in to prevent exactly what's happening?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "it", "President", "Obama", "who", "went", "--", "he", "sorted", "the", "mess", ",", "did", "n't", "put", "the", "regulation", "in", "to", "prevent", "exactly", "what", "'s", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "A lot of people -- a lot of people thought it started way before Bush.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "lot", "of", "people", "--", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "thought", "it", "started", "way", "before", "Bush", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WDT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "These firms are already in their heads too big to fail, aren't they?", "question_tokens": ["These", "firms", "are", "already", "in", "their", "heads", "too", "big", "to", "fail", ",", "are", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "But I have to -- there's one part that we always miss which is part of the culture itself.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "I", "have", "to", "--", "there", "'s", "one", "part", "that", "we", "always", "miss", "which", "is", "part", "of", "the", "culture", "itself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "How do I and all the people like me who really don't know about this stuff -- how do I know this isn't going to happen again tomorrow or next week or next year?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "I", "and", "all", "the", "people", "like", "me", "who", "really", "do", "n't", "know", "about", "this", "stuff", "--", "how", "do", "I", "know", "this", "is", "n't", "going", "to", "happen", "again", "tomorrow", "or", "next", "week", "or", "next", "year", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "Great question.", "answer_tokens": ["Great", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "How do we know?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "we", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "I think the sad answer is it will happen again.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "sad", "answer", "is", "it", "will", "happen", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 709, "question": "What was the germ for this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "germ", "for", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 710, "answer": "I would say if I had to point to one thing it was probably the financial crisis and the backlash, which is to be expected.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "if", "I", "had", "to", "point", "to", "one", "thing", "it", "was", "probably", "the", "financial", "crisis", "and", "the", "backlash", ",", "which", "is", "to", "be", "expected", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 724, "question": "What do you think it is?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "it", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 725, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 727, "question": "Why do you think America hit it's big financial crisis?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "America", "hit", "it", "'s", "big", "financial", "crisis", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 728, "answer": ".", "answer_tokens": ["."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 730, "question": "Do you think that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 731, "answer": "Well, I'm only 11.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "only", "11", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 735, "question": "what do you say?", "question_tokens": ["what", "do", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 736, "answer": "I say, it's complicated.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "say", ",", "it", "'s", "complicated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "This is all obviously quite complicated, right, you don't understand all of this do you?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "all", "obviously", "quite", "complicated", ",", "right", ",", "you", "do", "n't", "understand", "all", "of", "this", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "Not all of it.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "all", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 748, "question": "If you were America's President, what would you do to get America back on its feet, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "America", "'s", "President", ",", "what", "would", "you", "do", "to", "get", "America", "back", "on", "its", "feet", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 749, "answer": "Well, what I would do is, I would encourage the businesses to get back on their feet and --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "I", "would", "do", "is", ",", "I", "would", "encourage", "the", "businesses", "to", "get", "back", "on", "their", "feet", "and", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 750, "question": "What about regulations?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "regulations", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 751, "answer": "I'm not a regulation inventor.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "a", "regulation", "inventor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110519pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 768, "question": "Will you characterize it as grotesque?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "you", "characterize", "it", "as", "grotesque", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 769, "answer": "If I made it without anybody else suffering because of my actions that's perfectly acceptable.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "made", "it", "without", "anybody", "else", "suffering", "because", "of", "my", "actions", "that", "'s", "perfectly", "acceptable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]